[{"topicId":"4","id":"4000","langCode":"en","question":"J/ubf1/hq1pirK885j2nhCMBWRbRrQTQ8yjkEAWq3PY\u003d","answers":["much","an","many","a"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"kuUeOotlOKmNLek9d2EQU+c1bIY9/AP4wl6tn3SwJx9EM2BFfjZktfjG9n2jPLexoV/d4wksV60KH6WiDYnPLwn0R+iKzzcdHdqSOedjHUwtLZetZpwegnDqTMEH7dJyCBB2ydtQKmy0KzXrKI9xJnUswxu8JYZpEP136PXPBSt8A+B8b2sAJE6NAhp6MvTfmZe1CO9zjQuBWxXawMpwOdiBGjQolxRdzq1s1r+DoXXxbIcHVuc8OZ7cyoDnnGP1SiA42jTAXBw5Gj+vvqiUGujP1wKcnPZb94Jf4pCnyO4\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4001","langCode":"en","question":"ZkjEgEvHTc8rcB2p5gINk4y2UMnMvsNBjjYLfntTveL9XLqpVPrSy/rL61xY8Wd446xti0QWxleWZn+LeX5g0w\u003d\u003d","answers":["a","many ","much","an"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"KZI250TZ779hQT3wppTXiGXPGrU4QZUx1bccCDZIiTYj6PgM1X36jpnskRjfproc8PEx958qItSfaeGV7V52I6gjXmwy8b+Ql33OV1ID+7BHT9tzT0PMDE37qMcLxbFPevm5Rxek/SkDZLnGI8mZBnr8v9vHBGinjfv+W9j72SiJRRRUoUmUFOQOKkK8so+eh4NJpt71D9eU5K2p2a1owk60WbeHlT91WLDB5rmXc3mHjVBUAAe0k8z9WAplf34229C5B9OplZSyuexUdvMIuxaPU8PPEzO4j1vTOzfu1cJ0ZBL942Ia1iOrQuEsty3mB+RSRymt81WxZi8fLnrAUC2Wq9g6tQoghOksl7AJJhk\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4002","langCode":"en","question":"tm7XfV0SA6InQBDf/pSWh+dPPtpoRnnLWJIJDtEcFWjKuv1D34Yz3uYpKcoYMr0CxqL9QXhc84h+KL3z5aha8g\u003d\u003d","answers":["some","many","an","a  "],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"O1Koadgb10nqtxJbElatIwcZbIJKdrpOTcDUd5ZHIwt1C6zG5Q/oybbv1Hoi88bnJpfDv+TXBIJWnUJ7AK5Tjbcf1U/hFZEy1SQgomFzW3oo8ASMt4ZM4+imsgZCBoAjq2G4O5l6VuQmYN3PFYeUkkdd9KaxUXOpAjrHrE98WxGW6ugpo3NvfQWWS7F0Bpa0JXivkur+tg1S5qufXEx5wpcfWwQdUI11tVeXKLGKVQntlgY+E8R2EQhaBoC0yNTF5Q1AeXp4zJkAFUX70QXnNeMepodorFUEhX4M7hpw3W4\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4003","langCode":"en","question":"TYlVLFPr0tlwcByUWTPPmu1FHB2Y8jh9Z51wlQhL7PvuQXzxHIXLT5A8elAMjLFWfb2is/7v0q9q5UYTvtIa5EzM0T9cng7XOBuiXF3kNiQ\u003d","answers":["a","an","much","many"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"N8Dg1I6uEwfQ2dFxK6igq1maCR9g7GWg2QAr0An29s9V/NAs3R5Jo9aH5eejwwcI1ViXitt6ZgN6GrmWx+VCdETyc2IblaicVigaa1KvbWcaNYKNQyQlVJKqsstj78akw6c7W1sL1ADIQD4xgbvZuLGlJMU+dxFFS72fvKaoPq4Ctrjr/695JgQuTzZ/UqUKX2hMfo63p3GHU/j2vz4ckDq+ZTa1cJSu1lB47jyxNoK+WJrX1UcmtJJrvWrJGptexUtWN1NxnSlD4ESQlt8B5m+DXdlvdG8jWRWrS0sUJl/2Ks/ZBmEuQtgfCC9p4D5hezt2nx3jYK2B0oGfKSCE3n5y3DHNZDNt6F9hOJ+96f0\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4004","langCode":"en","question":"DTT64kF0nqz8i5KCxL8QNAKxqLB9SFWXFv0F0mu3jlWrH0RI1xZI9E6njUxCK7tcG9pUe8dzaMmb3etxzQhT1A\u003d\u003d","answers":["a few","many","a","a little"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"fA6r5iaH5cJiAVlPk9SaBuEhFrfVGC0G4UuCIgrlt30MRcEBBjO4a25xleSFPrN1XxqMvT08x1PuRwaKY5owf7vuosbOL77fqDQpgz1ZL4ki9+A4tGvn2ZUniK5k0kQuNlRr3oHiUL3R6+zFeayObUhNTrjUaYrYkrAcw1FC0uDp6RJd7qESEI53U9wQLImM2vZun0/J3BE6KWpxPvbgs9zXqTOqVgHKuVWftpGb0IB1AGps0cyWTpU5f7/h5nAtD+dPYXxcYQtiDwpgtxEEDuIppBgLVyTsUiW2Wg3bjXV5Y9wiPG8CflpJuBCClz46"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4005","langCode":"en","question":"tlJLMIzy01JA7GNzj49l2psHGh2fUmm9QxnfbIjgQ0Cg46EyZo/gLWGEILEKBw1B3YaTzyUdlqDAXYXZHlX8Ckff7CSjpc9CyKZ6lwEEimY\u003d","answers":["many","a little","much ","any"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"BShdZ4nFf5czvkDbiFZP/rFRnwJnKHwQJTX6d0AAkQ9OpkFXaMoRgT4Fw0poYipK5hQuVKmlT/lMguapttlNuZy+y0UGqDJWSgRmZokfwmgR2hF5tTZ0Y/51nL8/b6lPnNCaOVlxG1CCM7od67r61qViWWyfvL452kwfSMlXO0XP39tvvh2lYEJM3IfkldVMncR7r2/Vu9hwdllbpjmbVZrubvQHdoQpWWOabq/GEf+EY/mehVc4CEAUROGNwdH8B7NcDw/mxf1gwvVqUCgu/g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4006","langCode":"en","question":"7Skzl2UmD4dSnvBvfnaTMl9cdttlV87Ig8a5yoLi2itZVq7CEV1ygt5qDRzS/D4G1QxyRNB+AdQusabJESiddHV+0ygvWOKjLMoH4W6qnAY\u003d","answers":["a","any","some","an "],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"doqmjJ8ftJlNvdH8hAWFOReNg+ezNEiiLK43KNfg08dOb1dZJKYM06HoBjgjQl1UNQhQzXg+NhaZHISbHyI1/E0FiP9zz/36MxNA+VtX8aCN6doq6Qrp6zG24XU0ExfsMOvCbNQZjCC7pRX+vM/tbwyqdgez5nx1BwEBHTyvT5bwxNrGw4c35cgZb9W0PNYQVaZYZwimJKdgaMLfpyfiNY5YdS71zhKDAG27aTRbRJ0\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4007","langCode":"en","question":"9U0cbitLGb9ZY5ciwXxpN+qgH0fmuybfXeWKiwKPlBw6Om4Su7c71MtT64oasygHwaNzwB3o9kTGQ91fmgmsc9Mpb2Evpi3UmboUl8juM7k\u003d","answers":["an ","some","a few","many"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"4XsLw2XNGMLRrDd/7OeS6IHHv6UtMkTt9Xvny85vtLnzt5z9d1utwLwELiBcZrsu/Ha5AqsfXV6fZrJSLSnYg0WwOktDTrK0vqDezavbQj4q9GlVG/FlXv8sIYPbXjY8kHmQYMjZ9xxNDYiSHEneyT9O9JW+uemdpmZ0P/1Zgh/J/328ZOXEMoT+5PUFHt7JI72LpK9bomUCViH9myeYNSA8i6FvxWfrUyIMhYQEeDQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4008","langCode":"en","question":"qt3OHmE5E/7FohR/tGuTLF66IVfxNl1ujGTKpn5F/SvgpAidNJ/M8CnPuUcpz0Qn7Myf4o1gsnnkWW2szdQDiQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["much","a little","a","a few"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"Dwt7s23DdJec7W3FEpBQNNVdYxQ9+4ME8QGGioFaXqlgnkn2GWethzJh6n2UJLNKkFPpSLgvqoGpp639zh/hXbJ28tkcCn5BhwuTxIbRWWumiw/4lysKgd9ICHk+TSZ461d/b9l+wvx9TGx22u9FOJ5pJt/uQ1AKGIrZXw1BCjc\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4009","langCode":"en","question":"V4Pn/y7FHWt7JSyvR1ezvlSRM5TTAXfMuhbyEaDotUtbcC1kE9mr9ypr33Ug2/p5","answers":["some","many","any","much"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"ara9+xJlYHAzXrivQV8rleYNQHlNzEbtokWuL2ApS2mVkikFtfeByHy55J25NpuFH5IL0EdIrYJQTfILUTZkIw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4010","langCode":"en","question":"9yAJc/WBJ4UTa8lUqYfj7sNwrcswPNErt5JeCwJNFr7ABZGh8ZU0Be3MMfZ9XWHMYXUDx4WrswGg/zQKzanfCP08guDoYENYwyHZy2Nkr3M\u003d","answers":["any","a little","a","an"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"O1Koadgb10nqtxJbElatIwcZbIJKdrpOTcDUd5ZHIwt1C6zG5Q/oybbv1Hoi88bnJpfDv+TXBIJWnUJ7AK5Tjbcf1U/hFZEy1SQgomFzW3oo8ASMt4ZM4+imsgZCBoAjq2G4O5l6VuQmYN3PFYeUkkdd9KaxUXOpAjrHrE98WxGW6ugpo3NvfQWWS7F0Bpa0JXivkur+tg1S5qufXEx5woHYPub38CJrDwEJFT7ml6IWSi2xDk6MFqGA8PrIHY342pp2xDa/yXz99l/JOasd4yEkzU8zfG8hPLAbMgjlaTk\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4011","langCode":"en","question":"TIxi7UDy3P3w7v2TzHfs/lLikIzClkJ65RonIT1zqcviXzb+GLbmm/WWJvwspi3+","answers":["a little","little","much","a few"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"OfEA8vh0D6Q/iDn3VJT9S50LS/1u9iKbaHlgnAxR7sP6Qk6P88nJvL2azYA41jQEnzDxXmJBeOgTHpE3fFsR5z1PTY99h9URIlcqc7FUxZoZUm/l3vyF2DYHRXy4CHpYeYjBSRzYjXsXSWG7+qNZMxzMbkOKfAYIqg+8mretx+ajs9QGOTnv6CinwSVaSAHY"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4012","langCode":"en","question":"uCnQkABmnPdd/ZpR7rL+g6vvHlHTV4GQvFIm3li2rdBEABnIKsMHHomB+dprG4X6VIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["many","a lot of","a  ","some"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"pAB1sRBKJDH/hiGWQ3QK0Svt5AFkq6s8rh4uoysZRXSLKy3VmU4jmoqecOj2os3VrL7lAcSJZXeLAsgmvlR6zaWCqQQz0DV6IMOrVS/bxJ1jxLXRcJI1wtkdFahi2Nw6C8uEZeNJ3b7tT1bqatV/RhHKvZs2KDesbTNry4qN7OqHxh5XJ3+4Bx3V9r92zldz2oy49wll6H1dD1NoZQzmDMuinBn1hN20wXt1XtRhZ7Nk5aBMEa4OzclPqor8HJA+TDQJ9N4PHnuS5hieFISEIQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4013","langCode":"en","question":"Tx0KnK2vh8WIjO5AMCCGV2E01HUHFJP+zKjkuC3zCHrwd49iSxMZi5CBvt4x0PKI","answers":["an","some","a","a few"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"IT5Nz6nOOVvZOUcuVDF4pdQzFMycJN/IS6iFadOuulq8tJ8q+q91crpr0aotECoR9pYHmKVojp056qjPl1dI+lX/Yu6LYjJAk9dqPQAVX7pwVooIPIllXXnUF6ssZJoCAVl0oWpw5f1ATnS/pmZVqbDxCyWPca+NRU6aOKlRrGisJNdijvo5h+r2trJfJ+gdr6vi34g0tGb8+XzTD9fRsQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4014","langCode":"en","question":"4uM1hxstMzXrryz9S2qjpg0Jgw6hayP3Ixls9ZUjSNdwPedSnb6F/4c5JO+9mafcwkxoecAtKIxbq3QZGBU+Fg\u003d\u003d","answers":["many  ","a little","any","a few"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"/Ly+ouEe0RoLev/Wo386uX/Zob8rS5egkBNU5YStIfigRB5dR97i74/njDBjrY2K9LmCiTSSS2D2hZB22lSqQavZ+5Egw2h+083FyWBZIiF50EV30uE1OHvoFyOb2aco5gEvHax/ri/8UtaFMvIQUXA41VVrnAggttF7fWiXlw2Pcji9EbvUvevtVY5kuSvb9SUFTOgQRkkQcmpu5oJoIATrJM63FpaBH8nyN2EbsNEgu4RRjSAArIGXPHqD15OLp0/BCbkcCGac0a1L2P4RgY6aA+MbRyfIiNzeXDA3IIdTY0BdgS5CdPQacqboDNEdfwc0SUPD5mFkZm9Fx49mpB33MZl6t12RDQh6/4MaJ6NguPM7l2ZyIPRe+gFE4S/GUeg/kEkjH7xOsxrz/M8ZuA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4015","langCode":"en","question":"TXdEeQsTl1LEcZANQxrMLMi0HbP3xEz1pBL5z0uqa3LA4Ld2TE5iDpI4898s8GUAFlQ3KBEljuH4V3gsqAg1eTHlcL5JxN5NsYMHwfVfGRw\u003d","answers":["any","little","much","many"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"R7YI17at7/hLnYXkOZAX7OKVgufCCv1C+GchJoIi9b7FJ4rvTEAOD/KEmwEsn8Cc"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4016","langCode":"en","question":"e26GdBXScfmQ3/vWylDT/NzHgf0ahYKa9m5HLbA1a2d8Zx6NLp/2BFTjJSvRiBTpXMqqP4+Xc/mus/Pc3qk8C4RvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["a","many","a little","a few"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"aCr5QDHXs4zcMDRoM+dMC2/CGYrDWhJcQLoT3K9i+jjqdgy4k1ZQmbyFF+mZLtD1F3xUpYdlSEFhbXoCtzSohXOMYsL/VcOwdEZQ35WYnBnPh8+vHVUJWJQ5MOkbjx4P9dW4DRI9fx0Izw8yf6JDnHODoFR5laBruTbrgaSeBJPxj8zM0HELGYABj9N2IV9MmloPMfniw5dc/FTpKjB4U92aoTy8qLK4vLp1HyR2Mw1UxItU51cIWS3k32lXiI4Y"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4017","langCode":"en","question":"AxX8Wu7xzPyMPaKaXsSooyWeEdfO1EYa9eUhy0RLMB1vbMNldjCafq+pzt/lG5evQZAOxAd/Tr7hJ8PIe6x5ulZpjAnOeQcK5H/PWN6zXGk\u003d","answers":["any - any","some - any","a few - a little","any - some"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"6TuDfv273SOOqrAx4CwamS2gcHkIh4NfaJqMt2lxANS40MYPQJ4iJPzSw5BGSVWd5X4MWg8yxvnRwlqR5dz/KCXeJAAmCTjO+E1YMqW5ToyapMlS1zinMLKszJUgZvRqrzHiSBKhqRmcL8KbiabAIshZGqh/rM7tt41rmflVLk5Wh22x3p9ujh6PGBqyzuhy/w0Hv+VVmOkmi/cNbFzlzH6ID8q8dZAW5USJyKIY0LVerEfiR4gEhjv2+MeojEW6KH9hQwMuBeCGphZmoeuEl9OVhHxSKvEQr5uTd6u+ST3o4H5fsS67juyz9DALcMyTTW5LfHYy4gWNtPbZv9Dl4Pz6SMuE5xchODxi5Q+jWhA\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4018","langCode":"en","question":"r8CK4h05+YvgHmOG0DWOFeIvIYQgEWNFEZHBZ3qZiXLmqSE3qEo/glPR756gAl6EijBJW1/EEw4ZpB4CB3JwJKvm/58pkHewxIKJg/dK8Y0\u003d","answers":["Some - a ","An - a little","A little - an","Any - some"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"twbIuWtxK93OsEKkhm9pu0a/Wr3NWvAlNEPuolTG4RxoUGYAi9JkNd3bcUGkbltCR1mB5QOdufpN+axqWuGXLbtlBd9X1wO4s+390DOdlyHncC4U3p29zIlFvupqSIUpFZzhUgNVB9vWMaxjr2TKgZ8c+1DcrmCleZ36sRRIPLk+9yChKOQSkFZDBFXGmDIt377C0RZVPp6+p8ew3+Mz5MfCqKVcYeqWAWcAgqdVx8PyVQyD2XJUxR78euLyglfA/hEx6VpQg13MX7+YgLuRDnHqnSYmgbUZDTp4hMPmE6xibelh91r6MQJfHqv8x78O/soVQHnN6JudpQlTICNDhHiWgW5mInEP+FLXZiMG7JU4IXl+RRSqK/EMBYVILwJtl2WnwMHIgjK4qB4IuQep4gWILNXga1Qif5FHYmTUAmOjX+XfM3Q+CGcv39cUVk64p/EgcTjASP49dVdhm4bv0w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4019","langCode":"en","question":"Dpf73t3N+yQ87iJNW9Tgx28bd2FyYZJ1aHXBhPLfDmwwJckQRFpXGQdjSeCylcOghG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["many","some","a lot of","much"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"NH1imsXrJA2alMxHQ/yh/9++V8RBJ2MiKbC2mMGjJQL2NfvDJd6wRHd6WpUpS5XcwCkvf0/NiY0i3Usdn8VNCyZwaGSaNsxFrW27qRd4b1bfF72RN/FrzIif5qNv2xkOmCIz4gmhzHrA7gIQTh/OThvz9umltcBuQhsqx5VDoGf8b4byh1+An7U0NsKO7jzILbImZWi3slPn1Mx/0eL1Ow\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4020","langCode":"en","question":"vd6HPxABVk7xSpTgwAZ06q5vc092p2WQ684Bg5/rwbWrAHGUxVhuHILq5JpUh5T4yoqQYoAn1LmahKesJOolURhZj7tyfeoyIxuSURLp8d8\u003d","answers":["a few","a lot","a little","any"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"06KL2qLrcAIOLpmQNos/H8yCA+rr+wDL/u1rbdj7s4kq8fLkFk6ngvRg4jxF1m9tXuRVykumH7cJ6fDOxj7kLKe6xYZ9RuXRnV7mRW+AB1WskbgQj6IeNZU7MhFtX0jOxPJwdG+VOgazTEUdtF0B/thdp/BRNKT9EK+ms2NwRp8wKhBFRcIjVMdj5yBI9wo8cYebeD7Sn9mSDTnsEs1SXO+YvP94oUEsY15OA+RsgdOfbyxHNpmjrJMstAhc6J88d/CVFZDUjUfS6+0HeYcUL1UsWhHUaY6B1i7ZfLbNIE0\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4021","langCode":"en","question":"x1uQEV7sbBQM65LCiU/znu+lldcrxn07amVp3+xedbRQVV//ODJkqMcusBFwtt/UiUl6FvCtPw/HJdFCjMLtgifNFabZv/tSAV6HXt9/3pY\u003d","answers":["much - any","much - some","a little - any","a little - some "],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"+eidQvhw75qZ1fhVL4lPv3ooSQsc3sE9DZbEYcPjEpzaoG1fid86xJ2pT3tK7kKsvA+ObZiCFiQdhL8baZqc7kY+tD/vQcIg1MCg20ycuIdPTfFmc2E58/5tFxCHtt7NdCyDT4rhnyvAPcXu4WnubuhHDaV9Tzw65qxPE68pt+yJaQyvL3GQLN3851SUhA4vFz+xvWwsG4XvIiV7jWhOlWWhFqtESMAFttoObbxdza6clMauMt3R3J+h5sNl9MlyWk2zYtiuX0Iy9YqgR5pPjF8FBvphQcIZfO3UJIVSRmAj1fvai7W8e9u0ptUjV7AuSLqAvGmDfndHraqVLLn1tRYlC/hOhW5xpd2thlrlNcr/fg4ftYwGZWlLPw8Wl8rfJR6l90EP11DWg8gE6rwEq/f56PB5+HrrI9gdwPcyWk0clTqA/pVYpJ3wkHMyKrOEVZuDdJLmFUv8W/KSfD357g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4022","langCode":"en","question":"hjEt2DzwwmQdiSfsOpNixVVepJveroa1zMro7sR5lO+XrnshdB7BO5Q/Xov7a9op+/L6yVw+MtH4yUz4PE0P6hO4IVZJMT3JFD18cnD2mME\u003d","answers":["an ","many","much","some"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"B5oGnJrT80bglYiBYamIaeYNQHlNzEbtokWuL2ApS2nKGjNvba8kGhPs4SbLDmLfzv9FooNBgz4Urs0GIKIReA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4023","langCode":"en","question":"c5Mr+48B8OvaC3gc0hQ2CerYiSD308BqtBn/jkHBDsYumzXnk98izlMiHAK/AcTTv+m83TGtTp7m96Fy6lmQBQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["many","much","a little","a lot of"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"Ba/TB/TdPLOAMf3BgA8sfPddqN+U9HBUB1DriQUuNyc2UXp2qHQ6W8PE+wZds46U9AkRiBHEoiUXNhHVwqntQ0qxZ7Vc/FTYemISUOH9NIqQIaMRM6AvlpWxzZqqMqOxBKmBVNF123ntnEOp/2CoMe9CPuQEzNLwqdULYO0epUoRBjLj4UAJiQQDChKafwcs"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4024","langCode":"en","question":"CIiTff56OBilStA2kjz/KxkXNPy9+QwJqtTR5aAHGy0BH1Zmrirwqf7mZab/5758+9oxDTNLB/Nmdmx1ZH3lm1pMheSzNxPKReTS04TCnmM\u003d","answers":["a little","some","many","a few"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"Ba/TB/TdPLOAMf3BgA8sfPddqN+U9HBUB1DriQUuNyc2UXp2qHQ6W8PE+wZds46UeUmEum9NyMQyOZNHBMP4AhjBx9RRNBJ89H+f5QQgjo9lo4J7iUjAefCEnb32SnepBeCWh80rIaRbHoGjAzhcRt77XlFP5Ui1xQ4cnUj5e3G1l8X6Calq1nuYlPC9pvJmSzJKYbsQxJNnTSk64SNOJg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4025","langCode":"en","question":"B2+oyerS5LG7sOtV0Mjb0j5QDSsGmtl3TZFQCiUkIa7GHcg6q9fhzUoeTymwro23VIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["many","some","a ","much"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"x6thYeOLFU3TyNJ3YqTY83HWma/8JdrEmJVU4g8YvGyohJ8PdCZwEce6nJGQUXrW8FH9ZpZg2kDqotVZd1jJ4++HgAMU9ZpVhHBpFvTMESSqWpZtT9Cfdp7ZIkpl96m7r7SL4c18125HdytsYgzjUEfs2+PojEVGy4RQ5RAaSeIrvsJRbkdtNlcCsZDYBRqStjUeHiMr+fxhUII8ZOOwNQCivDCEwlKxsWH0gomPKSz4kw1rtwom2kSjeY08WKC6kql55PdCiPMsd9c9olXKo4qNsHFrElgyJzx4CFjMIh5Trf942MhG/bpgKnh8uYhw"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4026","langCode":"en","question":"+TUSrYAK8g15XYCA2ZNV4YodtbD3gIFbg/a7lPg34ciSbXsF+fRdpwotqyarzCVU1FBUt8nMcIkQup3eR1YuZ3ayie+uvFF4x8MoKHJxSIE\u003d","answers":["Little","Few","A few","A little"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"OGNEuCe3lgFAgfYddhTpDUJYC9gUm0Fd2jHu33FYHjdoMQZA8NLx8STWdAeu/HrhLX0OymP7h3hVx6zyrdU7pbtFFwWhslJYdS2CRM52rM5aViahC6I8CtzZk0RcsKyYOTposdq2t41rdgA8I+m0GuwdUDgUC7qNFuAEmQ1R1z0KHMYGyesGPsqziphqQz4IFPrp+Wf4ueDAj7zfjRxkRl/5887s4T2XQBHrwCQkzhaxLDTA/XCv5TbFhtiS7RFGqAn4rQpajX4FcmFaSY/0Fjf5z6wq39IdndKQmAtnXIMIZxqv9f7jVtFwXaobSV6fcOzZG0o7vgC4wJwAY8HegzHILWas9K6n+ou4JYc//3uNbC8BCjmkng0REg9QKNBVZpx2shdOJaNfs41f9TuOnNZOi6zFG9tyaJTxxuOGMpO2iRa6d4chXD+vDeqCQ5oVdyiedRjMFj7Jd6lAak8+PEx5hwJrNfxZVLkbBwBw4MR8pR+f3MNsrbli4NnkcGA9"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4027","langCode":"en","question":"K7fsSeZo1Ot0m69+BwYd9PWcs469b3kw5+7fWripo3J3RbZIu0ZfKKlfKRPvl9GEPLEiRThp9r/oUJsvLSgT1daPUgU0KKvPSpMhCo9ta8uS1ST/TvHZwRh4CshN7/DH","answers":["less","fewer","more","some"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"pzsMvy2bOzZHxpATD18odxlO/I1QEQam7NGg91+UgkxKFwSfjjvqvsCj0xsqZqOfJ6+1RP8fpvGAQ6winYuerM5mCrELIbMJ7RsFYuDg2RrOnkXZpEYAxf3w6VyV/Tdc+2Np34gEkqhkbU8bgimCbXmIwUkc2I17F0lhu/qjWTMrileklpBGJGyT12F4PgCl3NepM6pWAcq5VZ+2kZvQgAmP/G3kRMGsWhARQgKhZiZzl+rNsOYAiOEhEct8QafXlpwdxNwW3nlHPA8+ZwF3pMnu8SxmJi9AEUO9z59zqcQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4028","langCode":"en","question":"L7/R65Qs/li1J+/7nEkPiLITFaXcH7Kr+7F0yPmnGVWWo1haXFBWTvTqpD8esxcBD1kYAfQV3m760wIrHO1BotN7LRtcg7plxyX7XKsya08\u003d","answers":["Much than","Fewer than","Less than","An"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"pzsMvy2bOzZHxpATD18odxlO/I1QEQam7NGg91+UgkxKFwSfjjvqvsCj0xsqZqOfJ6+1RP8fpvGAQ6winYuerM5mCrELIbMJ7RsFYuDg2RrOnkXZpEYAxf3w6VyV/Tdc+2Np34gEkqhkbU8bgimCbXmIwUkc2I17F0lhu/qjWTMrileklpBGJGyT12F4PgCl3NepM6pWAcq5VZ+2kZvQgJ5iZLazd6opKPfnIskLtLPTAd7jnecLcFEXOVCfFtFH2R59dTBf1ZryUSCFbgS6tb+/uhTUxhXyVaADbh6Wb8rLXeoj28G6XI7b+XAhoqIJ"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4029","langCode":"en","question":"p0o5CIxrTs+bCZShOzFsdxgNorOE7BsLiijrjP1O6M3QIpDyOWPJBS0GnzhAfwLm7QlUWusbjXqtOp/kGz17Sg\u003d\u003d","answers":["Little","The number of","A little","A number of  "],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"4Yw6sfB9Ymwqv/PnrpKyzR2SIOKW5OU1N352ptJ7JY4jdUbFUhPOy7YxAPVzfNmGRB1ZtAUyHSQYc6hwjk5xXc0n9Fjmr7O/z/o+gjWFThk\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4030","langCode":"en","question":"Esc8OphWlxZrqMhl6bWF63d8eLdFh4ryO4KFi+PK501qANCEGHjeQreWKkl/2/bY+7+jshKvcnXdUUHNlGi4OG9AOIP2TrUdEdBFhwUYyrlUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["Most of the ","All","Most","All of the"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"f5dkercoxk0gdrPg3vcPedjRn6hX+xHonMGcR/BzQo25zGAMc0MP5oSo3oPiEDZyeYuNqGDOLDB5Bhh6QsmtdLwLKZSJ7f/1wkSHN0+GH6qpHuKn1PLQ/iwpSu8Onb9CugeY0pUn5DRV3t2qhC7mvc0gWEZIqOs3s45sL9y85NQIil9002cC1IHtNCQ3ilaaI1GUqJmrFp1qmCs0Ejw+dWC/ZvqLbD91XA27HIlJ5jfBaUFaQR45hCzHIPXlNgo+zSOyvwfw4W8Qt45yOAOZRn6FNY3jflv/ktZxa8lSsjRaV2x4vyhZoD8xUkcp91mD4x6mh2isVQSFfgzuGnDdbg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4031","langCode":"en","question":"QK/7oYvm1iAkyv6QOOCHS7GiOVD0pPKC8lMXoueznQyGMcVyX76gakdmzWnunjaN","answers":["some of","a number of","all of","any of"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"u5B7purGU5MDR/n4alfKgwnUDxVx3YqG2mahQy134QU1RTekzpvHXQyCYMJPK5LD2F6qz32Wl8qULheGiVtXqw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4032","langCode":"en","question":"minEH3QLe/+lZDwk9jtyrT86oKAy30oWrIqqAQ1Zv5lndnLD9eoIwKP5A9BuPb1e","answers":["little","a little","a few","few"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"by21qk8DYbp06lKEkZaqic+J8njd6yn5hXft9gXJi918ez81gHJ6ppz9p8bgAUzOdx2ekfckA2TIl3vAV1teI5Nr2ygwSIBwzmMj8V4pbrtrpIqSr67DIFaab1Ditt+LnLUbxvLxWXhcC+We6c+VmId9OavmuPAMyoV0a0n+qXHYNYPiUX1rcWVEmKylv2kY+Q4SgODtPHE5QawFXWjPgLRNCrewURduOUf1XW7JamXyp1mRwdTszUjlSKCGQ72wQSGfk4K7GaZwjSfA6Shb68IcKSpQ5qvvaDMT06tUzcImtOLQdUv3X1TDWiInNgjbnPNncFQnNweEQ/qWA5hb6DghoG2XiggCXlC3HUvReW56zp6vAIEKeJ93n32MJcLL"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4033","langCode":"en","question":"3mPDqyrkL0tGWCM8+7kb0e9Zbh7eoziBd2ygOu9x2L0EFD8mtNhLrSZ/SBnClPkG6Bsh90DCS+JwsDM0D4SL3z8W295tF3vLbtOTKN8Vt1Y\u003d","answers":["much  ","each","every","many"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"0kSvzOOq+Xx5O5YzzzAxPgM6mHipQEmBkznqRRb7nOSP5tnnc5QX3YNoXeBBQ0Dh"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4034","langCode":"en","question":"hCVzzvsEs5K1mhoPVnNlNr3VaQnxeMlPEuPO349QVk5+1kxgK5hI9YBhri9bA2XWRLh5Ppm1k/uveKXj//GwX5d1N8e81JmSixQbJKqI2v4\u003d","answers":["Every","Some of","All","Both"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"O5rKa5RYDx/ew05lDFscjGSymL1TP+WUwiFb4oU9P9CRPmQwi27EEydu0c1mOecydSRHpMEBbmpP9lFllTKiWSeQeEa5NP616E+po/dwLgW5cr+dnkGWJ15ZcUAsEvitEb6bliChRZeF5GubVDZyuyITLkF1BYKBgjTpPZdo8Tlh72fxKH6bIGnjU6EdclUzEs+qy3Mb9GLdAzn24WcfWMZhz0ZUZnTBrVknbnzpy6OpnmzCA8RWB7QWaSc7IP/NE+IXKvAWqDDjkiYpaQKDekNOsc73+C2RUvrEf60PaWdLThypDIEqk8xjhC+HEsDIsDlfV75/IRRR46MuzzY8rLOVmUdhBPdf4TKWSWCAdWy0ZtvhDLBQor7oY5/HONDWiWZLL2+pj9O3DIfNFnKdTQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4035","langCode":"en","question":"+7imuMECScFTrEeY0botA68gOlbmBVuSaT9D6xAaBvw/wQYICdtHyToz1ZlZflF+ZEStd5Uq91MRwB8A7ZhuKQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["all","none","every","some"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"O5rKa5RYDx/ew05lDFscjGSymL1TP+WUwiFb4oU9P9DwKsEaE0MtdowiRpuHlv2pt34dHFuzb/s577RTj2ytrkVqtOPtB/CW8C1nI3Zif+3iTNyeZIPqpMQ9zTle+hh1f6+m3pu0srXTszUpR75m5Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4036","langCode":"en","question":"bezTOYqx8Ae3yWjbl4fx5FPufmVh/f3R8Zf0vtlq4eP+nxjUK49VddeV9g1Flyx6FH1uAD625FJ50fgSkIDAv5DZCVzyROXiocoORWRTLE8\u003d","answers":["Some","Any","Both","All"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"cqf4wOkmJC1wUd7km2zCisw6QGLJ1u/Ae4Sqt06pKyw\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4037","langCode":"en","question":"Bu67CNcFs2vpLsGAp8B1rEZHCF/QMEzLpsraL+DUME7OAZzsFlXg8cWm1FOMsAktGZJarzdQAINHhVTH5BMxkV2CuD1QPjpBKRl2wTK8sRuEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["Both of the","Each of the","All of the","None of the "],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"JaiT9WPLpJqldoIOsUMoEOirW3fJf17j3q4gjHfq10mtzmD9aPla/k/q7JQBrppWm0zqz8j1PkM2SywiX0JRCZMllBU35fvaSYDRHBvwnk0\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4038","langCode":"en","question":"iL/spF1u6AKtKJxOaYeu14cTczh/W8jUPqQf4ow2TUMxqVHAK8Kd8IEKak1J3ePNyAwq3qO4o4Bp7GcPosEEQQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["a great deal of","a few","many","a large number of"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"SmvBrax1m99Rh5U0252/D8XA8tBWa5/rgRS0KrrgjyVkvj2L1PsTNEY9PNzxeDy8EIKBORdiYt59KXCjkzkS50+LIFO+rx1bN8Lvx1mqPj9EN0zjBhGo1Des7mqekzV3iZ6SyyHG2iK+HVtefpWLuIiculOU8Tl/7jNNJ683UytSRJDDhDxUr4D+rMcbtaFi"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4039","langCode":"en","question":"Bwr0uJ70o+qpsxvLYvrBSGNErBh8RbItr5ZfyPvUdVFmTK5nQpm3PwwmDJvQAaborOAcUAzX6WZ1ABGSsv4+XQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["Most of  ","Most","Much","Much of"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"f5dkercoxk0gdrPg3vcPedjRn6hX+xHonMGcR/BzQo25zGAMc0MP5oSo3oPiEDZyeYuNqGDOLDB5Bhh6QsmtdLwLKZSJ7f/1wkSHN0+GH6qpHuKn1PLQ/iwpSu8Onb9CugeY0pUn5DRV3t2qhC7mvc0gWEZIqOs3s45sL9y85NQIil9002cC1IHtNCQ3ilaaI1GUqJmrFp1qmCs0Ejw+dWC/ZvqLbD91XA27HIlJ5jcc0xO1shqFwF7mBmw8qtkQK++uxUBRFlzZjBokRhmsnfJshJs4TWWNI8KoVHRUura2dTahTXWkaUDON1y8iOXbYn5e9MegHLHX5IrtOYCbHYpM6D20MCaMsdsZ2c7L52E\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4040","langCode":"en","question":"tBKod1LBjB2oC1Fmq/dM5zG8gtnk+VYDd9sSryxfE4TX/8ST0SNNBhfvS/yaOBbqYvx6YFSjS6xkM92lg5I2CnDUWjaj+CiV1dzK8Y9l+YM\u003d","answers":["Most of","Most","The number of","Many"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"f5dkercoxk0gdrPg3vcPedjRn6hX+xHonMGcR/BzQo25zGAMc0MP5oSo3oPiEDZyeYuNqGDOLDB5Bhh6QsmtdLwLKZSJ7f/1wkSHN0+GH6qpHuKn1PLQ/iwpSu8Onb9CugeY0pUn5DRV3t2qhC7mvc0gWEZIqOs3s45sL9y85NQIil9002cC1IHtNCQ3ilaaI1GUqJmrFp1qmCs0Ejw+dWC/ZvqLbD91XA27HIlJ5jeEapPOJu+y5n/Ceag1K1MV5g7yMx7+W5tAvkC8DQQ797tajQgCsCyczWWBVx23z8sc7Oypsl9cLEc4fSnNbE8rCkCSWP5BXqF15WtDGNk6uAPUiiiPyD7M0n2uG01Y2o34NEpfkfVQsmz+niX/fFDbenXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x12Tqva7pNIFfNVfPe4L6VIKEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4041","langCode":"en","question":"PYlLrSjhHHDsAw0DblH1DcMxXa9cO11yoWTV5TxjLZYJGf7ZCa5Pf65JEtx7pL96jX9pSFuh20sp0dg8aWG0i70yQwkq7mZLNn033C5Kz2M\u003d","answers":["Neither","Both","Either","All"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"VuYVpdfN9UOvKOyeX5Zod2/tjS/YDpgTTNRDl3wKq5vwIu17S4jJu0b4OHh9ZCZg"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4042","langCode":"en","question":"eZ2e8eyEO072IeyhHLsWL9m3su24N4ioCdXWI1ruQxh5xAh6Sob+IhPCYsHEChtUJLGPxUylyItTk5E+Jfan+NVgFzoFGjpys8f5VnIiWJU\u003d","answers":["Neither","All","Both","Either"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"VuYVpdfN9UOvKOyeX5Zod2/tjS/YDpgTTNRDl3wKq5tkRyTYkANvnGs+/lDNpx9I7Yszfef/kSBfCIMPeVay3aUDY3V7GWLU7Zhus6BvZpn+zP9UgK5URuiq/rP5AQaNfl/Q7poIyP46pO2a/UkmeA+and40pFyRtRHqu8t8LRG6VXU5UUGaBCOWvfjvkgcuWeQqPvHNbXrih1sI4q8YKkWyTUoJiBFM0lPfvFv8Y1t+R59DQbA0kkwzb4caACTfoRLtbOsR3YpKO0TbpLoHiSZle/y2525tm4pcs0gHQx0rvGyL+queHPQft6Z29c+M6K3XKFQhXsu3zAG2F2r10Ey6E/Y6SavYSYgkPZx0gho\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4043","langCode":"en","question":"XMMgJQBPYvTGgM+8eMYP1+DdTLH1eztIqyX2871DacQaqwk5pKhR93vpH+foGIKjSy2K6D0K5dChuwLWQ7Z4mGqU78c5+c1RNHCVb6BK+yQ\u003d","answers":["All","Neither","Both","Either"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"VuYVpdfN9UOvKOyeX5Zod2/tjS/YDpgTTNRDl3wKq5tkRyTYkANvnGs+/lDNpx9IqLYBvZdoBjVfrBRnNk5L9nDwQtLu9A496MIy9r+MktD1gwCjkZP1ltYzr1bpG8D8DcyAtdYVLlBakiKzWjvZL8/UXSNfj2yzFE6ex+9OGPaFfwXU+nnaipdOw1ykG8TbeqLz1PKNxpOE52eB1UrHKb5ThZMOPE7HTJqbE1B/DiBBlw5l+iVLV1dcOcgoiCR6zQwiSijWcdv0ZywYJC9gx8/eZEdsi4ridd+2yAQtNqB4P/rZwiyrzEEZ1ziDYrIe5/UQgerao6yadngadYOajyo4eoniGQorzXstkN9CYi0\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4044","langCode":"en","question":"8zb5w5PanbhiQsoWoqMlgEBtHOemzl/zbk5bEEeqriQf1d9H/QNMD4grR75ePFlervQwB5pxUi/UNTzQO5Rp6YRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["all - any","both - some","any - some","some - any"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"5RZBqsLaaVfDR1/11tl5Gy2gcHkIh4NfaJqMt2lxANRTOMtKlew2diyEgrD4qLxtNl04t8OQEuxCzzvc3+3Y35MMsEiOxme/5ltZXlysK/X4kw1rtwom2kSjeY08WKC6kql55PdCiPMsd9c9olXKo7fciJ0qTeRMSp8/vpKKGQBQy+SGuvfmFTcD7wVzwj4ZSF17l89/3nyBhqZDrWioUo3lc+8Yjx0sG6Yi3Mzbg1glYuaMVbx695w+ORoah0FM0udc0A3eq6IjXB2FT1zvqw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4045","langCode":"en","question":"qm56CujIP29m3yoB1HLxV7vzbU9Cr74pWNnrFYuzrN5Yelsd40vYJaHX4fmR2vkZIvZ4pkLCDC1Y3BvXEnVr/w\u003d\u003d","answers":["few / much","much / little","little / much","many / few"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"t5xFfeyPyqyTrO8Mx+EZGJrA/zVgIzD37XUFDAYncYA7izVc0I21uiC7IXHMLw3eLlRVOM95IbG8xf2N/QQ3GmjyzrGi1edN5nZ0dOMy0iY\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4046","langCode":"en","question":"TJsIV0VF5DUw9Rdnj0EDykho8L+2z5zWAf2c0LvYYSvfSPvvmh4fk52Ax1hBvwJhJjl9gf2GpuOjP5MZnBoWFXuORz8OhqYZ/LrXLZe5RKwotzYAlxqVHmRk+IHn5X6s","answers":["the number","a few","the amount","a number"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"FY0PTVPrBsP9WO/nkbPYgd++V8RBJ2MiKbC2mMGjJQIS3nx/alDi6Bt6U0yDxTMXvOu5LMIfOgNvosVreez758xizl8kyN8U7BXf4sEW5U06TC3http+BQ+TPjIneztz1aI79WRnCues99OqWhrlNHOyV/YTT+UbaTa4klQ0amA\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4047","langCode":"en","question":"vdHJR/juFudN6k67UZxiwS8aUyCeaD2jkcUh5zQZ57Zsrks0d29cIGQvajUZEq60WCnP4uYqTYpIfWFkiVwS67dBuKuaxtcMje46sF7E1AcwE4uy5dCM0N+9uWDqYZGn","answers":["most of the","the most ","most  ","mostly"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"f5dkercoxk0gdrPg3vcPedjRn6hX+xHonMGcR/BzQo25zGAMc0MP5oSo3oPiEDZyeYuNqGDOLDB5Bhh6QsmtdLwLKZSJ7f/1wkSHN0+GH6qpHuKn1PLQ/iwpSu8Onb9CugeY0pUn5DRV3t2qhC7mvc0gWEZIqOs3s45sL9y85NQIil9002cC1IHtNCQ3ilaaI1GUqJmrFp1qmCs0Ejw+dWC/ZvqLbD91XA27HIlJ5jdYuU/emeArm1RoM2VaDTBOCwkQ6U7qq2dUTseJLRCP/O6l1hO8058JsRo2QdCAWCj9QMcJ8TLQNLiww95hoP1JOGfEfJUaCGURaPIjd2B4lsIYjnIfO4UGxI29niw9/+g66vxnpFNElFX3B0fLl6414rK2Y9zoG5H8KE+T14941GTloEwRrg7NyU+qivwckD44gwNZlPZe7t2UYxOHxb6YR8bOnnlQWpvlnqhNDbLvb54YtW4aBbHvosUXmu4redI\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4048","langCode":"en","question":"sBjoWUjftHknvP6DxwWLEV8zRVSmjby8lGPoUdK5gQ60ulhGUiDKc6fxsE28H3Zh1nv8zD2blE4Gi1nUaxHnDRIo1YMUnYpdMlHFkFH9I18\u003d","answers":["fewer","little","more","few"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"VJ7g6XED0TDG2RbmTSZa/2h6FxUgagv/1QSf/rclo6bgbCLPmql5NFGuaZ2YRJ0h7gY19g3WeMLznyFX/G537FqZs+P6CipQPZ/UM/BLR5c8RflhsFB52QxXSYtTuOxcqtra26klbfETD9sV3Z7CXTf2Uh/LRnXPdiT4svzeZy52vqzY13rBHjf0LvO8Q75T+oLkjEMrWjDlDa/h/P4NDd6yDNJpFUpAW3CuoBpQMH+rsNBXmOMIU6MhWmUcZ8V5yu1qCQhbVYAV/9Xlo4vE9m66NuoVzNJ5V7FZzVh4qfPu866pFirQ7T7gYyhq+KaP"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4049","langCode":"en","question":"qP2nHd+RAwTBUWqbVr39MgIiIyFffUng+0cr+iutNNY0M5wQlfvFIxsh2fzgrh++3B6NLyA8HLLQvtlenlaWVniUTcK77p6GBkqvji3LRbM\u003d","answers":["A great deal of","Most","Of all","All of"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"TRRsWUbPzshpWfPs5L3EdoUIrUyiFp9+M/WiAn7HOlGhwKoVJljqjlGa2PPFByDOuY4RkgqqmXc4kgTBP/xI+kfTsVu2f40IlX3s1kLeQLHuhkGY1t7oWZY/PPKKcu1PRYAvKLpGNCAG3czyFTZDpsngF/5PsDCB7FNZsIegk2SvyJsetkUwwYpDBTLb+2VuyHfNzVmi6SiLhutJ1SwD+A9nxfMq+iWSEhPpqMil1J8\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4050","langCode":"en","question":"RhR2rB2KnLPuRnQaJgkIemCBK48kCv6YGL/J8az+pt6BvR26wxsOqbo+GlP+UF6ufSwF31cFpj38XEjTgC74SpA8SDuXweLkj5JNyaFYat2RBiuFNGkezR6h/33KnSzp","answers":["a lot of / a little","a few / many","a great number of / little","many / most"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"m8UYjqM4jRlJorchK6WtNe9w4BqAPC+pZYDn/eDd+CYcd/72D6JxZAAZsBMExjFXTCq0UbQmegkEvcvoFo2W1cb/JPtXfc4hYeQi3IztUijNJ6lGvwJh4kJZ08YA95/kzYaI3cTKrOD3O0L9jxqeDavS9IUe+A51+gDN1Ko4pFvK31eHVhLhu45Lv6SJkP7b/9mx0jikosLw9rsVNGJi2w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4051","langCode":"en","question":"TAQMQ0pblfPA3bTcdd4QVpAOyGnksrwHHdX8Z8n0iauyD8+ukNB7qhIkWq0p79Wl","answers":["a little","little","few","a few  "],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"OGNEuCe3lgFAgfYddhTpDUJYC9gUm0Fd2jHu33FYHjdoMQZA8NLx8STWdAeu/HrhLX0OymP7h3hVx6zyrdU7pbtFFwWhslJYdS2CRM52rM7deDG1r2fzYJGRkXrjGSnqpdJSlZiCvu5PdvBSbisuC5haP/q3ZvT/HiZZ0993uR2ZOfTj8CyvlOFpF9I60ocxWdwCuSzS3x6JKMcOyaeW1+RHYMDpVlzGc5LsyGtR34RY/KHpuCL3s8OtcFnwcLnBPny8kN+3JS0f65VOVZ1l0VBsAlvgZ+jRfsQMcRnVLS2bwFd6ks5X9Isid8V9zQVxA9mmeCG5c0cRlwoPE00V7W0dPa6ChqGRDMa/2INznkD5zVKlPlhQjiOyMj7R7RIKAw79/CgWqf1rG8fkPy4zgWsSeVYl0l7UNICFJXtxCaXKDZJwZZWPc58VYM0APIowi4RUo/B25SYO4uu8Cs7dAZxJVSncxPSoQf3nOvzfOKakiguqhVKMdYl0gt2fkgnBugUj3ckSCmT6jkLaLs84XwznYoek58dB2dXu+hJiHA0\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4052","langCode":"en","question":"GfQPHyoh/5yCTrLE0fT0Vf51i9OJYLCo+Me23fN+lK8cpdL5Ltx0CyYQAoYFcHekoM2bYSNXngWVwlxJ51cCIQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["few","a little","a few  ","little"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"gk08QvwNW8d3Ij5yzwLa6PRLbToktzPARkAPyO8ioyNES9VXkSYNUjJaRqX//cbbqQRYlZqb1/CWWcbbg+SiqagjXmwy8b+Ql33OV1ID+7CbOMbiVmNoQIudoXFvYtxgPJYyahAtLM0sBK1arwBWlpqqyt2c+u+3lUXPpbHfCoFsPLjUoJv9LU82wnY0zl4+npl0dNaBJDvZmVUFAwpH/CPRAYkM4aXSQzHX9i/MxqS5y6LB98G3bejzWSJ1VghjxX5hWi+s5cc5qYHENX9D/zIk7nn3tFvi45a84lG7jCIxBqLRA4Apfr8mVp+R+cGiIxwc8OJfKzHss9cLezL49H8HKduqHFQ9j+9/9UTgWQB5qgJdBXL05hcNXADlsieh/gqTLCqUBav+BoYLNmi4XkCIxPDqpmgL8DSTASnD7y9ifsPcQefBhLmirVBj8SHR6D9Q4HGtvIQvcy5pxB1Rv5AUCbudayaaAm3WuN5VxJuEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4053","langCode":"en","question":"BoXE5aeoed30lenCE1NMoSvZ2g8pStUXthuVYjuWMwkwQO5+/HFGPh5zQfhiefXDCjRCQmeOBjUo8L40T9/6PYQ/SE3N109JjXU83ntEtRuq8OG8jC1ndVInGZLkWWyo","answers":["A number","The many","The number","An amount"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"YbV/Pc7ZgPB7f8O7ZELw+KCvN1nHh0n8F56CVswRPcBXZeVOMXHoBdqLjmbd1U3Ov6054v6vExbicoN3gN01tPqD0cxQaLFh1ru8ldnZfndbEBYtB7n/uEefdwkt4Q++uYfM1nFEwsp22SjWH2NP0lEmwhzahp7zj3oicjdn9B3b7gSEPHdi8R1mpgmBvQZBusyqLCJboaJ69wn8mMAnSZAUHvx5Uahfxj6564zkhk+SZdpalyWFb6TKUz5oD7d/yg2ScGWVj3OfFWDNADyKMIWQilK6O3GdaJStAdFbEuA\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4054","langCode":"en","question":"SDLQ+DD8zihjECFXyEZ6t+v/rFm29xIHqAspeiNsJMCFGiScLnj1rtDecKI1BJfV7oe6fJdACQn9Pi+hiRyl0agSUYkhkMxcqfxqBIOfBPFUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["much","a few  ","some","little"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"zoY3xsgd+2Jve9uZWCEPjTlP78wkHteJopuWNaaLogoDmL+eZSxUZdouY/p5kDVl+UtU9dRPxsHvEHCHTFr87Hp5LR5wgmt2HQr/F9VRhuUzwtGfsOvTvctDdY2Yz4SlT/dL6hKBkQh4vI+ZL9R8nKJGhU7F7dDhj+2yQSdBY7rnmI4B0TKOM/0qORzijHwqkXGu1iyrGnfBj2TTT9/8Mg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"4","id":"4055","langCode":"en","question":"+VUEy9npepmzB+niInurdrCbZAg5iCXimUPpFeeAJipUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["a few of","many of","a little of","plenty of"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"lQW6JpxSNKgftPYuQwgziAwFBS5/mTtsbbrlwIzpSEYoImweN4dcpW/MLz4wWwQshcYbqGp3+3eEB8IkYQIS4jeklorZRUiWKEpOF6pNaQ8pII6eCXWEPhIm9kVipX1ptkLJQO+hMiNyyp4G6DunWIllgtjKh5RRgk+xKTCyLdY\u003d"}]